mercantila.com 2005-04-05

# Mercantila | Privacy Notice

CATEGORIES 

|  Mercantila › Privacy Notice 

Your privacy is very important to us at Mercantila. This Privacy Notice describes the information we gather about you, and the purpose for which it is used. 

You may interact with our site in one of two ways: contacting us via email, or placing an order. The kinds of personally identifiable information that may be collected during this interaction include: name, address, e-mail address, telephone number and credit card information. 

We also log certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit Mercantila, such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows XP or Mac OSX) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., Earthlink, AOL, MSN). We log this information using 'cookies'. A cookie is a small data text file, which a Web site stores on your computer's hard drive (if your Web browser permits), that can later be retrieved to identify you to Mercantila. Cookies make your use of the site easier, allow you to retrieve an earlier shopping cart, make the site run more smoothly and help us to maintain a secure site. **You will be unable to shop on our site without your browser set to accept cookies**. 

We use the information you provide about yourself only to fulfill your order, to enroll you in services you have requested or to respond to your inquiries. 

We use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to analyze traffic to our site, in aggregate. From this analysis we may make site design changes to improve your experience. 

We may disclose personally identifiable information you provide in response to a particular legal process. For example, in response to a court order, subpoena, or at the behest of a law enforcement agency's request. 

We require that Agents and Partners of Mercantila who have access to your personally identifiable information protect this information according to their stated Privacy Policies or in the event these Agents and Partners of Mercantila do not have a stated Privacy Policy, this Privacy Notice. That is, they may not use the personally identifiable information you provide for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for Mercantila - i.e. fulfillment of your order or enrollment in services you have requested. 

Mercantila uses several of the latest encryption technologies to keep your personal information safe. Your private ordering information -- including your credit card number -- is encrypted using several keys for maximum security. Your credit card and billing information cannot be sniffed as it travels to our ordering system (128 bit SSL encryption), and the numbers are unreadable to anyone trying to access the site remotely. We have implemented the requisite physical, electronic, and managerial processes to prevent unauthorized access, and maintain data security. 

You may contact us at any time to update the information we have about you. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. If you prefer not to receive information from us, either through email, postal mail or by phone, please let us know by sending us an email or calling us at (800) 718-1710 (8am to 5pm, PST). 

Please note that such requests may take up to six to eight weeks to become effective. Please also note that when you make a purchase, we will send you emails to confirm your order and may also need to contact you via phone, postal mail or email if we have other questions regarding your order.
